Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Damascus Road, Allentown, Pennsylvania, #2, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Damascus Road, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Damn You, Allahabad, India, #6, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Death, New York City, v. 1, #1, Summer, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Definition, New York City, #18, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Delta, Montreal, Canada, #2, January, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Delta, Montreal, Canada, #3, April, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Delta, Montreal, Canada, #7, April, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Delta, Montreal, Canada, #10, January, 1960-March, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Descant, Texas Christian University, Fort Worth, Texas, v. 12, #4, Summer, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- The Desert Review, Albuquerque, New Mexico, Spring, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- The Desert Review, Albuquerque, New Mexico, Fall, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- The Desert Rune, Arizona State University, Tempe, Fall, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- The Deserted Times, San Francisco, v. 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
- The Deserted Times, San Francisco, v. 2, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
- The Deserted Times, San Francisco, v. 3, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Desperado, San Francisco, #5, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Desperado, San Francisco, #6, January, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- The Dial, New York City, v. 1, #1, Fall, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- The Dial, New York City, #3, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Diana's Bimonthly, Providence, Rhode Island, v. 1, #1, February, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Diana's Bimonthly, Providence, Rhode Island, v. 1, #2, April, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Diana's Bimonthly, Providence, Rhode Island, v. 1, #3, June, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Diana's Bimonthly, Providence, Rhode Island, v. 1, #4, August, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Diana's Bimonthly, Providence, Rhode Island, v. 1, #5-6; v. 2, #1, October, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Diana's Bimonthly, Providence, Rhode Island, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- discovery, New York City, #3, March, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- DO-IT!, Cleveland, Ohio, #4, July, 1967-August, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Dog Bite, Monterey Peninsula College, Monterey, California, portfolio, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Dryad, Silver Spring, Maryland, v. 1, #4, Winter/Spring, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #1, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #2, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #6, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #7, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #8, September, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #9, September, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #10, September, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- duende, Placitas, New Mexico, #14, October, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Dust, El Cerrito, California, v. 2, #1, Spring/Summer (#5), 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Dust, El Cerrito, California, v. 2, #3, Winter (#7), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Dust, El Cerrito, California, v. 3, #1, Fall (#9), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Dust, El Cerrito, California, v. 3, #3, Fall (#11), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Dust, Paradise, California, v. 3, #4, Spring (#12), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Dust, Paradise, California, v. 4, #2, (#14), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Dust, Paradise, California, v. 4, #4, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- The Ear in the Wheatfield, North Fitzroy, Australia, #7, May, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Earth Journal Zero, Portland, Oregon, #2, Summer, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Edge, Edmonton, Canada, #4, Spring, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Edge, Edmonton, Canada, #5, Fall, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Edge, Edmonton, Canada, #7, Winter, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Edge, Edmonton, Canada, #8, Fall, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Edge, Edmonton, Canada, #9, Summer, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- The Eight Pager, Niagra Falls, New York, series 1, pt. 1, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
- The Eight Pager, Niagra Falls, New York, series 1, pt. 2, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
- The Eight Pager, Niagra Falls, New York, series 1, pt. 4, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- eikon, Portsmouth, New Hampshire, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Elephant, New York City, #1, Summer, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Eleventh Finger, Brighton, England, #2, Autumn, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Elima, New York City, #1, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Ellipse, Sherbrooke, Canada, #1, Fall, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- The Emerson Review, Emerson College, Boston, Spring, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- The Emerson Review, Emerson College, Boston, Winter, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Emily Dickinson Bulletin, Brentwood, Maryland, #30, 2nd half, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- En Passant Poetry Quarterly, Wilmington, Delaware, #2, 1st quarter, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- the end, Oakland, California, v. 1, #1, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Endymion, New York City, #2, May, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Enigma, London, England, v. 2, #1, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Enigma, London, England, v. 2, #2, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Envelope Magazine, Santa Cruz, California, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Ephemeris, San Francisco, #1 (and Cassiopeia 2), undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Ephemeris, San Francisco, #2, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Ephemeris, San Francisco, #3, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Epos, Lake Coma, Florida, v. 7, #3, Spring, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #8, November, 1967-April, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #9, November, 1967-April, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #12, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #13, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #14, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #15, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #16, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #17, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #18, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #19, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #20, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #21, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #22, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #23, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #24, July, 1968-July, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #26, September, 1969-October, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Esparavel, Colombia, #27, September, 1969-October, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Essence, New Haven, Connecticut, #43, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- The Eventorium Muse, New York City, Spring, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- The Eventorium Muse, New York City, #4, Spring, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- The Exile, Chicago, #2, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Exit, New York City, v. 1, #4, May, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Exodus, New York City, #2, Fall, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Experiment, New Orleans, v. 2, #6, Summer, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Experiment, New Orleans, v. 2, #7, Winter, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Expression, Harrow, England, #1, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Expression, Harrow, England, #3, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Expression, Harrow, England, #5, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Expression, Harrow, England, #12, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Extantis, San Francisco, #2, Summer, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Extensions, New York City, #1, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Extensions, New York City, #2, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Extensions, New York City, #3, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Extensions, New York City, #4, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Extensions, New York City, #5-6, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Eye--On the Denver Scene, Denver, v. 1, #2, November, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Fagrag, Boston, #9 (and Gay Sunshine 22), Summer, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- The Far Point, University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, Canada, #1, Fall/Winter, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- The Far Point, University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, Canada, #2, Spring/Summer, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- The Fat Frog, San Bruna, California, #14, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- The Fat Frog, San Francisco, #14, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Fathar, Buffalo, New York, #1, June, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Fathar, Buffalo, New York, #2, December, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Fathar, Buffalo, New York, #3, June, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Fathar, Buffalo, New York, #4, June, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- The Fault, Fremont, California, #2, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- The Fault, Fremont, California, #3, April, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- The Fault, Fremont, California, #4, November, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- The Fault, Fremont, California, #5, April, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- The Fault, Fremont, California, #6, November, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- The Fault, Fremont, California, #7, April, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Feathers, San Francisco, #3, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Features, San Francisco, #1, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Features, San Francisco, #3, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Fervent Valley, Placitas, New Mexico, #3, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Fervent Valley, Placitas, New Mexico, #4, Summer, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- A Few Moons, Berkeley, California, #2, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Fiction West, Santa Rosa, California, v. 1, #1, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Figures, New York City/Paris, #9, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Firebird, Yellow Springs, Ohio, v. 1, #1, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Fire Exit, West Concord, Massachusetts, v. 1, #2, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
- First Issue, New York City, #5, Spring/Summer, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Fits, San Francisco, #1, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Fits, San Francisco, #2, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Folder, New York City, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Folio, Birmingham, Alabama, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Folio, Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana, v. 25, #1, Winter, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Foothill Quarterly, Foothill College, Los Altos Hills, California, v. 1, #3, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- The Formalist, Oakland, California, v. 1, #1, Summer, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- The Four Zoas, Atlanta, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Fragments, New York City, #1, Fall, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Fragments, New York City, #2, Winter, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Fragments, New York City, #3, Spring, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- The Free A & A, #1, April, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Free Lance, Cleveland, v. 11, #2, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Free Lance, Cleveland, v. 12, #1-2, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Free Love Periodically, Cleveland, #2, June, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Friendly Local Press, New York City, v. 1, #5, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Friendly Local Press, New York City, v. 1, #6, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Fruit Cup, New York City, #0, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Fuse, El Cajon, California, #1, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- La Gaceta de Cuba, Cuba, v. 1, #71, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Gallery Series, Chicago, #1, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Gallery Series, Chicago, #2, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Gallery Series, Chicago, #3, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- The Galley Sail Review, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Gallimaufry, San Francisco, #1, Summer, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Gallimaufry, San Francisco, #2, Winter, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Gallimaufry, San Francisco, #3, Fall, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Gallimaufry, San Francisco, #4, Spring, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Gallimaufry, San Francisco, #5, Fall, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Gallimaufry, San Francisco, #7, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Gangrel, London, England, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- gaslight, New York City, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #10, January, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #12, April, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #13, June, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #15, October, 1972-November, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #17, March, 1973-April, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #19, September, 1973-October, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #20, January, 1974-February, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #21, Spring, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #23, November, 1974-December, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #24, Spring, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Gay Sunshine, San Francisco, #28, Spring, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Gegenschein Quarterly, Bowling Green, Ohio, #5, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Gegenschein Quarterly, Bowling Green, Ohio, #6, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Gemini, Oxford, England, v. 3, #3, Summer, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Genesis: Grasp, New York City, v. 1, #1, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Genesis: Grasp, New York City, v. 1, #2, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Ghost Dance, Michigan State University, East Lansing, Michigan, #2, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Ghost Dance, Michigan State University, East Lansing, Michigan, #10, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Ghost Dance, Michigan State University, East Lansing, Michigan, #17, Fall, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- The Glass, Lowestoft, England, #1, Summer, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Global Tapestry, Blackburn, England, peacefreak issues, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Global Tapestry, Blackburn, England, thunderskyglow issue, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Global Tapestry, Blackburn, England, #5, circa 1975 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Gnaoua, Tangier, Morocco, #1, Spring, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- gnomon, Lexington, Kentucky, #2, Spring, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Gnosis, New York City, Fall, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Gnosis, New York City, #7, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
- The Goliards, San Francisco, #6, December, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- The Goliards, San Francisco, #7, June, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Good-Bye, San Francisco, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Gooseberry, Point Pleasant, Pennsylvania, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Graduate Studies Journal, Berkeley, California, #4, Spring, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Grande Ronde Review, Sacramento, California, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Grande Ronde Review, Sacramento, California, v. 2, #1, circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Grande Ronde Review, Sacramento, California, v. 2, #2, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Grande Ronde Review, Sacramento, California, #10, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Gray Day Magazine, Macon, Georgia, v. 1, #4, Fall, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- The Great Society, New York City, #1, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Green Flag, San Francisco, #3, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Green Groad, Topeka, Kansas, v. 1, #8, May, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Green River Review, Owensboro, Kentucky, v. 1, #2, May, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- The Green World, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, v. 2, #2, May, 1964-August, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- The Green World, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, v. 2, #3, September, 1964-December, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- The Green World, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, v. 4, #2, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Green's Magazine, Detroit, v. 3, #3, Spring, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- The Griffin, New York City, v. 6, #6, July, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- The Griffin, New York City, v. 7, #11, October, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- The Griffin, New York City, v. 8, #3, April, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- The Griffin, New York City, v. 8, #4, May, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- The Griffin, New York City, v. 8, #5, June, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Grok, San Francisco, v. 1, #3, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Grosseteste Review, Kingswinford, England, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Grosseteste Review, Kingswinford, England, v. 1, #2, Autumn, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Grosseteste Review, Kingswinford, England, v. 1, #3, Winter, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 2, #1, Summer, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 2, #2, Autumn, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 2, #3, Winter, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 3, #1, Spring, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 3, #2, Autumn, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 3, #3, Winter, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 3, #4, Winter, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Grosseteste Review, Pensnett, England, v. 4, #1, Spring, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Ground Zero, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Gryphon, San Francisco, #2, Fall, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Guabi, University of California, Santa Cruz, California, #1, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Guabi, University of California, Santa Cruz, California, #2, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Gum, Iowa City, Iowa, #6, September, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Gypsy Table, San Francisco, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Gypsy Table, San Francisco, #2, Winter, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Gypsy Table, San Francisco, #3, Spring, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Gypsy Table, San Francisco, #4, Summer, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Gypsy Table, San Francisco, #6, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- H &, Hove, England, February, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Haiku Magazine, Patterson, New Jersey, v. 6, #1-2, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- The Hampden-Sydney Poetry Review, Hampden-Sydney, Virginia, Summer, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- haravec, Peru, #4, December, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Head, Staatsburg, New York, #3, June, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Head, Staatsburg, New York, #4, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Head, Staatsburg, New York, #5, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Head, Staatsburg, New York, #6, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Hearse, Eureka, California, #13, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Hearse, Eureka, California, #16, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Heirs, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Heirs, San Francisco, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Heirs, San Francisco (#9), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Heirs, San Francisco, v. 6, #1, Winter (#10), 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Hierophant, Los Angeles, #1, January, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Hierophant, Los Angeles, #2, July, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Hierophant, Los Angeles, #3, December, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Hierophant, Los Angeles, #4, April, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Hills, Cambridge, England, #1, March, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Hills, Cambridge, England, #2, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #7, Fall/Winter, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #8, Spring/Summer, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #13, Fall/Winter, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #14, Spring/Summer, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #15, Fall/Winter, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #16, Spring/Summer, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #17, Fall/Winter, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- The Hiram Poetry Review, Hiram College, Hiram, Ohio, #18, Spring/Summer, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Hollow Orange, San Francisco, #5, June, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Hollow Orange, San Francisco, #6, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- The Horbly Gnome, Edinburg, Texas, #1, December 1970-January 1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Horde, London, England, #1, December, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Hotcha!, Switzerland, v. 1, #16, October, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- The Human Voice Quarterly, Homestead, Florida, v. 2, #3, August, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- The Human Voice Quarterly, Homestead, Florida, v. 3, #1, Spring, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- The Human Voice Quarterly, Homestead, Florida, v. 3, #2-3, Summer/Fall, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- The Human Voice Quarterly, Homestead, Florida, v. 4, #1-2 (#13-14), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- The Human Voice Quarterly, Homestead, Florida, v. 4, #3 (#15), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- The Human Voice Quarterly, Homestead, Florida, v. 4, #4 (#16), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Hyphid, Toronto, Canada, #1, January, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Hyphid, Toronto, Canada, #2, July, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Hyphid, Toronto, Canada, #4, December, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Illuminations, San Francisco, #2, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Illuminations, Mill Valley, California, #3, Summer, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Illuminations, Tucson, #4, Winter, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Illuminations, Sante Fe, New Mexico, #5, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Images, Dayton, Ohio, v. 1, #1, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Imagi, Allentown, Pennsylvania, v. 4, #3, Winter, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Imago, Montreal, Canada, #10, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Imago, Montreal, Canada, #13, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Imago, Montreal, Canada, #14, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Imago, Montreal, Canada, #17 (Vancouver, Canada), undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
- In Terris, Peru, #3, October, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Inferno, San Francisco, #9, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Ingluvin, Montreal, Canada, #1, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Ingluvin, Montreal, Canada, #2, Spring, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Input, Valley Stream, New York, v. 1, #1, December, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Interim Pad, San Francisco, #1, September, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Intermission Magazine, Chicago, August 3, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Intermission Magazine, Chicago, October, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Intermission Magazine, Chicago, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Intermission Magazine, Chicago, v. 3, #4, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 1, #9, November, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 2, #1, January, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 2, #2, February, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 2, #3, March, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 2, #5, May, 1970-June, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 2, #7, December, 1970-January, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 3, #1, March, 1971-April, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 3, #2, Summer, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Intersection Newsletter, San Francisco, v. 4, #1, Fall, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Intrepid, New York City, v. 4, December, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Intrepid, Buffalo, New York, #19, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Intrepid, Buffalo, New York, #20 (and Floating Bear 38), Summer, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Intrepid, Buffalo, New York, #21-22, Winter/Spring, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Irish Writing, Cork, Ireland, #7, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Irish Writing, Cork, Ireland, #10, January, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- IS, Toronto, Canada, #8, Spring, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- IS, Toronto, Canada, #9, Fall, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- IS, Toronto, Canada, #10, Summer, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- IS, Toronto, Canada, #11, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Isthmus, San Francisco, #1, Spring, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Isthmus, San Francisco, #4, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Isthmus, San Francisco, #5, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- IT, Platteville, Wisconsin, #13, September, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- IT, Platteville, Wisconsin, #14, November, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- IT, Platteville, Wisconsin, #16, March, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Jaw Breaker, Westmount, Canada, #1, June, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 1, #1 (#1), January, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 1, #2 (#2), April, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 1, #3 (#3), July, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- John Berryman Studies, Derry, Pennsylvania, v. 1, #4, Fall (#4), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)